(Leonard:)Sheldon, sit.
(Sheldon:)Ah.
(Leonard:)Well, this is nice.
We don't have a lot of company over.
(Sheldon:)That's not true.
Koothrappali and Wolowitz come over.
Yes, I know.
(Sheldon:)Tuesday night we played Klingon Boggle
until 1 in the morning.
- Yeah, I remember.
- I resent you saying we don't have company.
- That has a negative social implication.
- I said I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)So...
(Penny:)...Klingon Boggle?
(Leonard:)Yeah. It's like regular Boggle,
but in Klingon.
(Leonard:)That's probably enough about us.
So tell us about you.
Me? Okay.
I'm a Sagittarius, which probably tells you
way more than you need to know.
(Sheldon:)Yes, it tells us that you participate
in the mass cultural delusion...
...that the sun's position relative
to arbitrary constellations...